( giggling )
ARE YOU LOOKING AT
NAKED TRIBESWOMEN?
NO. LOOK.
THAT'S A PIG.
I KNOW, I KNOW, BUT LOOK
AT THE KNOBS ON IT.
HEY.
EMILY'S COUSIN
KICKED ME OUT.
WHAT?
WHY?
WELL, WHEN YOU'RE SUBLETTING
AN APARTMENT
FROM YOUR WIFE'S COUSIN,
AND THEN YOU GET A DIVORCE
SOMETIMES THE COUSIN SUDDENLY
WANTS HIS APARTMENT BACK.
DIDN'T YOU
SIGN A LEASE?
WHO NEEDS A LEASE
WHEN IT'S FAMILY?
HEY, YOU COULD
STAY WITH US.
WE'LL TAKE
CARE OF YOU.
ANYTHING
YOU NEED, MAN
BUT YOU HAVE TO PROMISE ME
YOU WILL LET US KNOW
THE SECOND YOU ARE
FEELING BETTER
SO WE CAN MAKE FUN
OF YOUR HAIR.
YEAH.
YOU GOT IT.
OKAY.
THANKS, YOU GUYS,
I REALLY APPRECIATE THIS.
I'M GOING TO GET PACKING AGAIN.
I'VE BEEN MOVING AROUND
SO MUCH LATELY
I'M BEGINNING
TO FEEL LIKE A NOMAD.
( giggling )
WHAT?
HE THOUGHT YOU SAID "GONAD."
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
IF EVERY RESTAURANT
WERE AS CLEAN AS YOURS
IT'D BE A TOUGH TIME
MAKING A LIVING.
OH, LARRY.
SO, UM, DO HEALTH INSPECTORS
WORK ON COMMISSION?
NO. BRIBES.
IT'S OKAY TO LAUGH, RIGHT?
YEAH. I WAS JUST KIDDING.
OKAY.
I'M GOING TO CHECK
THE KITCHEN FLOOR.
OKAY. KNOCK YOURSELF OUT, LARRY.
YUMMY.
WHAT? LARRY?
OH, YEAH. I'D LET HIM
CHECK OUT MY
KITCHEN FLOOR.
A 98.
I DEDUCTED
TWO POINTS BECAUSE
YOU'RE NOT WEARING
YOUR CHEF'S HAT
AND THAT IS
A SECTION FIVE VIOLATION.
LOOK, LARRY, HONEY
UM... I WROTE THE BOOK
ON SECTION FIVE
AND I KNOW THAT
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO WEAR YOUR HAT
UNLESS YOU'RE
IN THE KITCHEN.
WHERE IS YOUR HAT?
IT'S IN THE KITCHEN.
I'LL GO GET IT.
THERE'S THE TWO POINTS.
HEY, YOU SHOULD REALLY READ
THAT BOOK YOU WROTE.
WOW.
YOU SAW THE HAT
IN THE KITCHEN
AND YOU KNEW
SHE'D HAVE TO GO
IN THERE HATLESS
TO GET IT.
YOU COULD HAVE
YOUR OWN, YOU KNOW
HEALTH INSPECTOR
DETECTIVE SHOW.
WELL, I DON'T
KNOW ABOUT THAT.
YEAH, BUT THEN I COULD BE YOUR
SIDEKICK, VUNDA.
MAYBE VUNDA COULD
GIVE ME HER NUMBER
AND I COULD ASK HER
TO DINNER SOMETIME.
OKAY, SHE WOULD LOVE THAT,
YOU KNOW
SINCE YOU KNOW
ALL THE CLEAN PLACES TO EAT.
I'LL CALL YOU.
OKAY.
HE'S SO FUNNY. WHOA. OH.
THANK YOU.
MON, HOW'S ROSS DOING
YOU KNOW, SINCE
ALL THE EMILY STUFF?
HE'S NOT GREAT,
BUT, UM...
HE'S DEALING WITH IT.
OH.
OH, WAIT A MINUTE,
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO...?
OH, HONEY, PLEASE, NO.
I CAN'T GET STARTED WITH
ALL THAT ROSS STUFF AGAIN.
HE'S GOING TO BE
SCREWED UP FOR A LONG TIME.
AND BESIDES, YOU KNOW
I DON'T GO FOR GUYS
RIGHT AFTER THEY GET DIVORCED.
RIGHT. YOU ONLY
GO FOR THEM
FIVE MINUTES BEFORE
THEY GET MARRIED.
TWO POUNDS OF MOCHA JAVA,
PLEASE.
IT'S DANNY.
ARE YOU GUYS EVER
GOING OUT AGAIN?
I DON'T KNOW.
HE HASN'T CALLED ME
SINCE THAT ONE TIME
WE WENT OUT.
I SEE HIM IN THE HALLWAY,
WE FLIRT.
I'M ALL...
( insincere laughing )
...AND NOTHING.
HEY.
HI, DANNY.
WOW. THIRSTY, HUH?
ACTUALLY, I'M HAVING A
PARTY AT MY PLACE ON SATURDAY--
SORT OF A HOUSEWARMING THING.
OH, FUN.
OH, GREAT.
I'M REALLY LOOKING
FORWARD TO IT.
OKAY, SEE YOU.
WELL, I GUESS WE WON'T
BE WARMING HIS HOUSE.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
I SEE WHAT HE'S DOING.
HE'S NOT ASKING ME OUT
BECAUSE HE WANTS ME
TO ASK HIM OUT.
YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO DO THAT?
THAT'S RIGHT.
BECAUSE THAT WOULD
GIVE HIM THE CONTROL.
SO NOW HE'S ALL,
OOH, COMING UP WITH THIS
"I'VE GOT A PARTY" THING--
YOU KNOW,
TRYING TO GET ME
TO HINT AROUND
FOR AN INVITATION.
BLEW UP IN HIS FACE,
DIDN'T IT?
SO THERE
IS NO PARTY?
OH, NO.
THERE'S A PARTY.
THERE'S A PARTY,
BUT THE POWER--
THAT IS STILL UP FOR GRABS.
YOU FOLLOW ME?
I THINK SO.
SO HE'S NOT INVITING
YOU TO HIS PARTY
BECAUSE HE LIKES YOU.
EXACTLY.
ROSS?
HEY, ROOMIES.
HEY.
LOVE WHAT YOU'VE DONE
WITH THE PLACE.
YEAH, I KNOW, I KNOW,
IT'S A LOT OF BOXES
BUT AGAIN, I REALLY APPRECIATE
YOU GUYS LETTING ME STAY HERE.
NOT A PROBLEM.
AND SINCE YOU'LL
BE HERE A WHILE
I WAS THINKING WE'D PUT YOUR
NAME ON THE ANSWERING MACHINE.
OH. I, UH, HOPE YOU DON'T MIND
BUT I KIND OF ALREADY
JAZZED IT UP A LITTLE.
CHECK IT OUT.
( playing intro to
"We Will Rock You" )
Ross:
♪ We will, we will
call you back. ♪
HEY.
ALL RIGHT.
PRETTY COOL, HUH?
YOU'RE FAKE LAUGHING,
TOO, RIGHT?
OH, THE TEARS ARE REAL.
YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL
THIS EVENING.
SHOW ME THE BADGE AGAIN.
SHINY.
YOU MIND IF I WASH UP?
I CAME STRAIGHT FROM WORK
AND WHO KNOWS WHERE
THESE BABIES HAVE BEEN?
YOU ARE JUST NON-STOP.
WE'RE OUT OF HERE.
WHY?
JUST WALKING
PAST THE KITCHEN
I SAW TEN VIOLATIONS.
I AM SHUTTING
THIS PLACE DOWN.
YOU HAVE THE POWER TO DO THAT?
THIS DOES.
SHUT IT DOWN.
HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
NOTHING.
YOU BUILT A FORT, DIDN'T YOU?
KIND OF.
OH, MY GOD, THE AIR PURIFIER.
ROSS'S AIR PURIFIER.
ALL I HEARD FOR FOUR YEARS
THROUGH COLLEGE WAS...
( humming )
YOU SHOULD HAVE GONE OUT
ONCE IN A WHILE.
I HATE THIS THING.
COME ON, CHANDLER.
ROSS IS OUR FRIEND.
HE NEEDS US RIGHT NOW.
WHY DON'T YOU BE A GROWNUP
AND COME WATCH TV IN THE FORT?
( knocking on door )
OH, HI, DANNY.
I JUST WANTED
TO INVITE YOU
TO THE PARTY
TOMORROW NIGHT.
OH, THANKS.
I'LL TRY TO
STOP BY.
YEAH, ACTUALLY, I THINK...
I'M GOING TO BE BUSY.
YOU ARE?
YEAH. REMEMBER?
I'VE GOT THAT,
UH... GALA.
WHAT'S THE GALA FOR?
UH, IT'S A, UM...
IT'S A, IT'S A
REGATTA GALA.
REALLY? YOU SAIL?
NO. NO, BUT I SUPPORT IT.
OKAY. WELL, HOPE I SEE YOU
TOMORROW NIGHT.
OKAY.
TAKE CARE.
WALKED RIGHT INTO THAT ONE,
DIDN'T HE?
WHAT ONE?
YOU WANTED HIM
TO INVITE YOU
TO THE PARTY AND HE DID.
YEAH, BUT HE WAITED
UNTIL THE LAST MINUTE.
SO IF I SAID YES,
HE WOULD KNOW
I HAD NOTHING BETTER
TO DO THAN WAIT AROUND
FOR AN INVITATION
TO HIS STUPID PARTY.
I SAID NO,
WHICH PUTS ME
RIGHT BACK IN
THE DRIVER'S SEAT.
SO, THE BALL IS IN
HIS COURT?
BALL?
NO, THERE'S NO BALL.
( rhythmic slapping )
JOEY, PLEASE.
SORRY.
( rattling )
( shrieking )
HELLO, CHILDREN.
HEY.
WANT TO PLAY SOME FOOSBALL?
PLEASE?
OKAY.
NO, NO. NO.
WE HAD TO MOVE THE TABLE
INTO MY ROOM
BECAUSE OF ALL THE BOXES.
COME ON.
ALL RIGHT, I
HAVE ONE QUESTION.
WHAT IS THE DEAL WITH THIS?
BYE-BYE, LITTLE PUPPET-JOEY
HAND?
NO, NO, THE "QUIET DOWN" THING.
OH, YOU MEAN THIS.
MM! MM!
I DON'T KNOW HOW
MUCH MORE I CAN TAKE.
DID YOU KNOW HE TAPED OVER
MY BAYWATCH TAPE
WITH SOME SHOW ABOUT BUGS?
MY GOD.
WHAT IF THAT HAD BEEN PORN, HUH?
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, YOU KNOW
THIS MAY BE TOUGH,
BUT COME ON, IT'S ROSS.
I SURVIVED COLLEGE WITH HIM.
ALL RIGHT. I GUESS I CAN
HOLD OUT A LITTLE LONGER.
LET'S HAVE A GAME.
OKAY.
NO, NO, NO.
YES!
( laughing )
UH, FELLAS?
( door closes )
OKAY, SO HE'S OUT OF HERE.
YOU GUYS GOT ANYTHING TO EAT?
I JUST WENT
DOWN TO JOHN-O's
FOR SOME CHICKEN,
AND IT WAS CLOSED.
I TOOK LARRY THERE TO EAT,
BUT IT WAS ALL VIOLATED
SO WE SHUT IT DOWN.
PHEEBS, IF THIS GUY
KEEPS CLOSING DOWN
ALL OUR FAVORITE PLACES,
WHERE WE GOING TO EAT?
I DON'T KNOW;
CLEAN PLACES?
MMM. YUM.
( knocking on door )
IT'S DANNY.
DON'T LET HIM IN. I'M SUPPOSED
TO BE AT A REGATTA GALA.
WE'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
CAN'T YOU JUST SAY IT
STARTS LATER?
WHAT KIND OF A REGATTA GALA
STARTS AT NIGHT?
THE FAKE KIND.
HEY, UM, I NEED A LADLE.
YOU GOT A LADLE?
WE HAVE A LADLE.
THANKS. SEE YOU
AT THE PARTY.
OKAY. GREAT.
HEY, YOU GUYS.
YOU KNOW WHAT LARRY WOULD SAY?
HE'D SAY, "SEE YOU LADLE."
( Phoebe laughing )
WELL, I'M DONE WITH THIS.
YOU WANT ANYTHING, ROSS?
UH, SPORTS?
INTERNATIONAL?
APARTMENT LISTINGS?
UH, I'LL TAKE SPORTS.
MINE.
ALL RIGHT.
UH, INTERNATIONAL.
THAT'S MINE, TOO.
I'M ITALIAN.
I GUESS I COULD CHECK OUT
THOSE APARTMENT LISTINGS
EVEN THOUGH THERE'S
NEVER ANYTHING IN HERE.
NOT EVEN ON PAGE SEVEN?
OH, YEAH. YOU'RE RIGHT.
OH, HERE'S AN AFFORDABLE PLACE.
TWO BEDROOM, CLOSE TO WORK.
OOH, IT'S AVAILABLE
IN FIVE WEEKS.
WHAT ABOUT THAT
CIRCLED ONE?
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S KIND OF EXPENSIVE
FOR A STUDIO.
BUT IT'S AVAILABLE NOW...
ISN'T IT?
YES, IT IS.
LET'S GO
LOOK AT IT.
OKAY, LET'S GO.
HERE WE GO.
HEY, HEY.
OH, OH, OH,
HEY, GUYS.
I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU WOULD, UH...
MAYBE CHIP IN FOR
SOME NEW AIR FILTERS
FOR THE PURIFIER?
I MEAN, AFTER ALL,
WE ARE ALL USING IT.
LET'S GO QUICKER.
( long, appreciative whistle)
OH, MY GOD.
MMM.
LOOK AT
THIS KITCHEN...
SLASH BATHROOM.
THAT'S GREAT, YOU KNOW
SO YOU CAN COOK
WHILE IN THE TUB.
SOMEBODY WAS
USING HIS HEAD.
HEY, LET'S CHECK OUT
THE REST OF THE PLACE.
I THINK THIS IS IT.
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE WE SHOULD
KEEP LOOKING.
BUT, HEY, ROSS, THIS
PLACE IS AVAILABLE NOW.
YOU DON'T WANT
TO BE STUCK WITH US
FOR THE NEXT
FIVE WEEKS.
YEAH.
SO YOU THINK
I SHOULD GO AHEAD
AND TAKE THIS PLACE?
IT'S PERFECT.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
KITCHEN SLASH BATHROOM.
UH, I SEE WHAT
YOU GUYS ARE SAYING.
I'LL, UH... I'LL
GO DOWNSTAIRS
FILL OUT AN APPLICATION.
WE ARE BAD PEOPLE.
HE KNEW WE WERE TRYING
TO GET RID OF HIM.
HE KNEW.
YOU THINK WE COULD GET
A BATHTUB IN OUR KITCHEN?
HEY, YOU READY FOR DINNER?
OOH, ABSOLUTELY.
GREAT.
YOU WANT THE ITALIAN PLACE
DOWN ON BLEECKER, RIGHT?
OOH, I LOVE THAT PLACE.
SO... NO.
OH, HOW ABOUT
MAMA LEZOTTI'S?
UGH.
SURE.
I WONDER HOW LONG THAT
MILK HAS BEEN SITTING OUT.
OH, NO. THIS PLACE
IS TOTALLY HEALTHY.
THIS MILK IS MINE.
I BOUGHT THIS TODAY BECAUSE I
WAS THIRSTY FOR MILK, YOU KNOW.
OKAY, LET'S GO.
HEY, BUDDY.
YOU FAMILIAR WITH
SECTION 11-B
OF THE HEALTH CODE
THAT REQUIRES
ALL REFUSE MATERIAL
TO BE TAKEN OUT
OF THE BACK EXIT?
BUT THEN I HAVE TO GO
ALL THE WAY
AROUND THE DRY CLEANER.
OH, SO YOU'RE
SAYING YOU CHOOSE
CONVENIENCE
OVER HEALTH?
OKAY, STOP.
LARRY...
OKAY, CAN'T
YOU JUST BE LARRY
AND NOT LARRY THE
HEALTH INSPECTOR GUY?
YOU KNOW, I MEAN, IT
WAS REALLY EXCITING
AT FIRST, BUT NOW,
IT'S LIKE, OKAY--
SO WHERE ARE WE
GOING TO EAT EVER?
WELL, I SUPPOSE
I COULD
GIVE HIM A WARNING.
THANK YOU.
OKAY, GO,
GO, GO.
NOW, IF, AFTER DINNER
YOU STILL, LIKE, REALLY
NEED TO BUST SOMEONE
I KNOW A HOT-DOG VENDOR
WHO PICKS HIS NOSE.
MAYBE... MAYBE WE
DID A GOOD THING
HELPING ROSS GET
BACK ON HIS FEET.
YES, THAT WAS
A NICE PLACE.
YEAH.
NOT A LOT OF
CLOSET SPACE
BUT HE COULD JUST
HANG HIS STUFF
OUT THE WINDOW
IN A BAG.
YEAH.
WHAT WILL WE DO?
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE PIZZA?
ABOUT ROSS.
OH.
( telephone ringing )
HELLO?
OH, YEAH.
IT'S THE APARTMENT MANAGER.
ROSS PUT US DOWN
AS REFERENCES.
ROSS IS THE GREATEST
GUY YOU'LL EVER MEET.
YEAH, HE'S
VERY RELIABLE.
OF COURSE, HE HAS
A BIG, HUGE DOG
THAT, UH, BARKS INTO THE NIGHT.
WELL, WHO DOESN'T LOVE DOGS?
UH, HE'S A TAP DANCER.
YES, SOME WOULD SAY
THAT IS A LOST ART.
HE'S A PIMP.
THERE YOU GO.
YES, HE'S A PIMP.
HE'S A BIG, TAP DANCING PIMP.
HELLO?
OH.
THIS IS NEVER
GOING TO WORK.
HE'S RIGHT THERE.
JUST GO OVER
AND SAY HI.
I HAVE TO GO DOWNSTAIRS,
COME BACK UP
AS IF I'M COMING HOME
FROM THE REGATTA GALA.
OKAY? SO JUST
GO DISTRACT HIM
BUT DON'T BE SEXY.
HEY, DANNY.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
IT'S A GREAT PARTY.
GREAT FOOD.
UH-HUH.
YOU KNOW,
MOST PARTIES--
IT'S ALL CHIPS AND
SALSA, CHIPS AND SALSA.
SO, UH...
WHAT'S THIS?
SALAD.
OH.
AND, UH,
WHAT'S THIS?
BREAD.
AREN'T YOU A CHEF?
OH.
HEY, RACHEL.
HEY. OH, RIGHT.
TONIGHT WAS YOUR PARTY.
YOU LOOK GREAT.
I'M GLAD YOU COULD MAKE IT.
OH, YEAH, WELL, YOU KNOW,
THE GALA HAD TO END SOMETIME.
DON'T GO ANYWHERE.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK,
ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, SURE.
ALL RIGHT, WHOSE COURT'S
THE BALL IN NOW?
I THOUGHT THERE
WASN'T A BALL.
OH, COME ON.
HE'S GLAD THAT I CAME.
HE DOESN'T WANT ME
TO GO ANYWHERE.
BALLS FLYING ALL
OVER THE PLACE.
RACHEL, THIS IS
MY FRIEND, TOM.
THIS IS THE GIRL
I TOLD YOU ABOUT.
OH, COME ON, YOU'RE
TELLING PEOPLE ABOUT ME?
I THINK YOU TWO COULD
REALLY HIT IT OFF.
I'M GOING
TO GO MINGLE.
SO, YOU WORK
AT BLOOMINGDALE'S, HUH?
MY MOM CALLS IT "BLOOMIES."
OH... YEAH.
OKAY. AT EASE, SOLDIER.
I'M SORRY?
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU CAN JUST
DROP THE ACT, TOMMY.
I KNOW WHAT'S
GOING ON HERE.
YOU'RE DANNY'S
WINGMAN, RIGHT?
YOU GUYS ARE BEST BUDS.
FRAT BROS.
I'M GOING TO GO TALK
TO A FRIEND.
YEAH, YEAH. YOU GO
TALK TO YOUR FRIEND.
YOU GO TELL HIM,
"NICE TRY."
MAN, YOU KNOW, HE JUST KEEPS
LOBBING THEM UP AND I JUST KEEP
KNOCKING THEM RIGHT
OUT OF THE PARK.
I THINK I NEED A DRINK.
YEAH.
98... 99...
ONE... HUNDRED.
OKAY. GO.
DUDE, I'M TELLING YOU, I'M FINE.
HERE WE GO, HERE WE GO.
HEY.
SO, I, UH... I DIDN'T
GET THAT APARTMENT.
SOME PROBLEM
WITH MY APPLICATION.
Both:
YOU'RE KIDDING!
YEAH, BUT THE
GOOD NEWS IS
PHOEBE SAID
I COULD STAY
AT HER PLACE FOR A WHILE, SO...
WELL, YOU CAN'T STAY
WITH PHOEBE, ROSS.
WE'RE ROOMIES.
LOOK, YOU GUYS
DON'T NEED ME HERE
TAKING UP ALL YOUR SPACE.
WE GOT PLENTY
OF SPACE.
THERE'S STILL SOME OVER
THERE BY THAT SPEAKER.
PLEASE, JUST STAY.
YEAH.
ARE YOU GUYS
SURE ABOUT THIS?
DEFINITELY, YES.
YES. ROSS,
YOU HAVE TO STAY.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT,
BUDDY.
HEY.
SO I'M A PIMP, HUH?
IT'S OKAY.
LOOK, I KNOW SOMETIMES
I CAN BE A PAIN IN THE ASS
BUT YOU JUST HAVE
TO TALK TO ME.
TELL ME IF SOMETHING'S
BOTHERING YOU, OKAY?
AND FOR MY PART,
I'LL REALLY DO EVERYTHING I CAN
TO KEEP MY ANNOYING HABITS
YOU KNOW, JUST...
WELL, I SEE YOU'VE HAD
A VERY PRODUCTIVE DAY.
DON'T YOU THINK
THE COWBOY HAT'S A LITTLE MUCH?
COME ON, IT'S FUN.
ALL RIGHT.
ISN'T THIS A WOMAN'S HAT?
DUDE, STOP TALKING CRAZY
AND MAKE US SOME TEA.